We are now approved in 65 countries outside of the U.S.
In Japan, we've already reached first-line NBRX leadership, as you can see in the lower chart.
In Germany, our early NBRX first-line share is already up to 15%.
So we're very excited for the trajectory of Semblix and to continue to be a growth driver
long into the future.
Now, with Cosentix, we had a solid quarter, 10% constant currency growth,
in part driven by some one-timers, but still strong underlying growth.
And when you look at in the U.S., we were up 16%.
You can see that in HS, we're steady in our NBRX share in the high 40s,
and we expect that to continue. We see steady demand growth in HS and IV.
Underlying growth in the U.S. is around the mid-single digits, as we've guided to in the past.
And I would like to thank all of you for joining us today.
Outside of the U.S., continued solid growth.
In Europe, we do see additional challenges in China with more competition,
but we're able to manage that to maintain the overall global performance of the brand.
And then we're excited by the Phase 3 replenish PMR, polymyalgia rheumatica data,
which we recently published and presented at UR.
It showed very strong data with sustained remission at 52 weeks.
That was twice as high in patients treated with Cosentix versus placebo.
So we're anticipating FDA approval for that indication in the second half
and remain on track for the $8 billion peak sales guidance that we've previously provided.
Now moving to slide 13, Rapsido continues its strong launch trajectory with Phase 3 SINDU data
now available to support our broader potential in urticaria.
First targeting, starting with the CSU launch, we see continued solid U.S. uptake over 4,000 units.
Over 10,000 prescribers, over 10,000 patients treated.
60% of those patients are treated in the first-line setting.
We see steady expansion in our patient access.
We have two of the three major PBMs now covering remibrutinib, Rapsido, with PA at a label.
And in the second half, we expect steady expansion in that access
with an effective bridge and sample program in place.
We don't expect an inflection per se.
We think this will be steady expansion.
We want to ensure.
We're disciplined in how we approach getting reimbursement,
given the multiple indications we hope to secure for remibrutinib over time.
Outside of the U.S., we see good traction in China.